I'm freezing.
It gets so cold at night now.
What does one do in this situation?
Run to the station?
No way.
Rub her shoulders?
That's sexual harassment!
Please use this.
Don't worry about me.
I'm actually feeling warm.
Well, if you say so.
Oho?
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 9:
THEN WHY CAN'T I STOP THINKIN' 'BOUT IT?
"Then Why Can't I Stop Thinkin' 'Bout It?"
The new autumn and winter outfits are so cute.
But...
Welcome in.
Can I help you find something?
We also carry these in other colors.
There's no way!
I'll just give up and buy them online...
But...
I still want to check the materials
with my own hands.
But still...
You?! What are you doing here?!
I'm meeting someone later,
so I thought I'd do some shopping first.
What are you doing, Senpai?
Huh?! Er...
I-I wanted to look at some clothes, but...
Um...
Could it be the employees?
You want to take your time
without being approached.
Is that right?
Are you interested in that one?
In that case—
We're okay.
I think she'd rather take her time looking.
Oh, is that so?
Please excuse me.
No worries.
What's popular right now?
Ah, yes!
I can browse the clothes
without worryin' 'bout anything.
This is a first.
Really?
Yes, indeed!
Um, excuse me!
C-Can I try this on?
I like this one.
Yes! It suits you.
Something like this might
be nice occasionally.
I think so, too!
I could wear this to work.
Yes! It's totally doable!
Which one should I choose?
I think they all looked good on you.
Wait! If I say they all looked good,
does that make it sound like I don't really care?
Really?
Okay! I'll go buy these!
Cu—
Ow!
I need to calm down.
Sorry for making you stick with me today.
No worries.
I had fun, too.
Oh, good.
Well, I'm heading home.
Yes. Get back safe.
Good work—
S... S...
See... you.
Yes! See you!
Was that too weird?
But we weren't workin'.
"Good work today" seemed unnatural.
Yu!
CAFFÈ LATTE
What's wrong, Kannawa?
What's with the long face?
PLANNING DEPARTMENT
RITSU KANKAIJI
Kankaiji...
You like these, right?
Drink it and feel better.
You're being creepy.
We haven't seen each other in ages,
and that's your first thought?
K-K-K-Kankaiji-senpai?!
Th-Thank you for your hard work!
You're Kankaiji-senpai, right? From Planning?
Yup. And you are?
I'm Hotta, from Public Relations.
It's an honor to meet you!
Hotta-chan, huh? Thanks!
You're as super casual as ever.
I haven't changed, but you sure have.
In the past, you never would have shown
that depressed expression you had a bit ago.
Huh?!
Depressed?
Is something wrong?
Th-There's nothing wrong!
You won't ask us for help?
That makes me sad.
It's not something worth asking for... help...
I understand.
If you don't want to talk about it,
I'll just ask directly.
Huh?
If you're this upset,
I bet Kamegawa's involved.
Hold on! Why would you think that?!
Isn't Kamegawa her junior?
Mind if I tag along?
Not at all!
Let's go raid him together!
I'll talk! I'll tell you!
I see. Kamegawa did, huh?
But hey, there's no way it's a girlfriend.
I'd know.
But...
Huh. So you're bothered by it?
W-Well, because he's my junior,
and he's important!
"Junior." Right.
Anyway, are you free this weekend?
Uh, I guess.
Would you like to go to the spa?
WE'RE GOING TO THE SPA WITH SENPAI
THIS WEEK! BE GRATEFUL! TO ME!
Something's been moving
along... somehow.
What is it?
Nothing.
Just that it's been a while since
we last had lunch together.
Oh. I guess so.
It makes me happy,
because it felt like you'd abandoned your
peers and switched over to your junior.
That's a misleading way to put it!
I-It's not like I didn't want to involve
myself with you guys anymore...
Why are you laughing?
It's just that
you really have become
a lot more expressive.
What are you talking about?
Hey, did you hear?
Lately, Kijima's been...
What? I don't believe it!
Right?
But it's true!
Really?
Whoa.
Sorry!
You must be Kamegawa-kun.
Her favorite.
Huh?
Take good care of my li'l Kannawa.
"My li'l"?
Oh! Also...
I'll be joining you all at
the spa this weekend, too.
Huh?
What?!
Hiya, Senpai!
Hello.
Sexy.
Why would you say that?!
If anything's sexy, it'd be the
maid outfit from that one time!
You don't understand, Senpai!
It's not something you show!
There's also sexiness that cannot be seen!
I don't understand what you're saying.
Hey, all.
Throwing "sexy" around
in broad daylight, are we?
Good to see you.
When did you get here?
I got here five minutes ago, as we planned.
But also...
Kamegawa-kun arrived even earlier.
Well, I mean...
Senpai's been telling me for the past six
months to arrive fifteen minutes early, so...
I didn't notice!
Did he hear us spouting that
"sexy" stuff this whole time?
Is this the right way to the entrance?
Oh, I can look it up.
It should be...
So you're her partner at work, right?
Yes.
She's a nice girl, right?
And a cutie, right?
Yes.
Right? She's cute.
Hey, now.
Don't distance yourself
from me so obviously.
That hurts my feelings.
Oh, I, um...
I meant that as in conventionally cute!
So she's not cute?
She's cute!
But what are you getting at?!
What are you two doing?
We're going in.
O-Okay!
He drains me. This guy really drains me.
You two are so similar.
What?
Did you say something?
Oh, well, Kamegawa-kun was
saying you look cute today.
What?!
What?
N-No...
I was saying how well your outfit suits you.
Ooh. Scary.
R-Really? Thanks.
Right? It's sexy, yeah?
No! I just said it suits—
It's the same thing.
It's not!
WOMEN'S BATH
Okay, Senpai! Where should we go first?
I want to try the stone sauna!
What about you, Kamegawa-kun?
I-I was thinking I'd try the sauna for now.
Okay. I'll—
Oh. Sorry.
This is a work call.
Of course.
Hello. Thank you for
your continued support.
Oh. Kamegawa.
C'mere. C'mere.
Looks like they have hair straighteners.
You'll be able to fix yer curls after yer bath.
You remembered that?
Uh-huh.
Senpai! I'm going ahead!
Wait for me!
Later.
It's hot.
Well, that's what this is, after all.
You can relax and let your mind go blank.
That's the purpose of a stone sauna.
I see.
Yeah. This is nice.
Empty my mind! Empty it!
I can't empty it!
Senpai?
Hey.
Is there anywhere that will
make me stop thinking?
I wonder if Senpai's
enjoying the stone sauna.
My li'l Kannawa.
That guy makes me uneasy.
He keeps teasing me for some reason.
And he... seems to get along with Senpai.
Because they're peers?
Even so, they seem to be pretty close.
And Senpai doesn't seem bothered by it.
Could it be that those two
are even closer than just peers?!
Wait, what am I saying?
It's none of my business.
I'm just a junior to Senpai, after all.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'm sorry. Should I use less pressure?
No, please press harder.
Will do.
Ouch!
So?
How was the foot massage?
Amazing.
I couldn't think at all.
Could it be that you're still
hung up about that?
Stop it!
Just when I'd finally forgotten about it!
So I was right?
Laugh if you want to!
But...
I don't know why I can't stop
thinking about it....
At this point, why don't
you ask him directly?
Just say, "Who was that girl?"
You know I can't!
Yes, you can!
We're off the clock today, too.
So you can bare it all to each other!
Huh?
But Kamegawa's not in the same bath as us.
That's not what I meant...
I meant it as in liberating yourself.
Let loose!
Hotta makes it sound so easy.
I wouldn't be this worried if
I was able to ask him head-on.
Kamegawa.
Did you come out here to cool off, too?
Uh, yeah. You could say that.
The breeze is nice out here.
If it's all right with you,
would you like to go for a walk?
Sure.
That was nice.
Right? The outdoor bath was huge.
How about the men's bath?
It was huge. My body felt like
it was melting. It was nice.
Th-The lanterns are so pretty.
Y-Yeah.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Um—
Y-You first.
No, no. After you.
No, sorry.
It's nothing.
Me, too. It's okay.
Should we head back?
Oh... No, I'll cool off for a little longer.
You can head back first.
All right. See you later, then.
Time to get serious.
What would Senpai drink?
Maybe a cold iced tea? Or oolong tea?
It's for Kannawa, right?
She likes this one.
Thanks.
CAFFÈ LATTE
You don't like me, do you, Kamegawa-kun?
What? That's not true...
No need to hide it.
I know a lot about Kannawa, and we're close.
That probably bothers you, right?
No. I'm glad.
Huh?
I know that most people around
Senpai misunderstand her,
calling her scary and such.
So knowing she has someone she can
open up to like she does with you...
I'm happy as long as Senpai is able to laugh.
I see.
You are a good "junior" after all.
But as for me...
I like Kannawa more than just as a peer.
I want to be even closer to her.
That's where I stand.
Is it okay for you to drink so much?
Totally okay!
Another!
Oh, boy...
And you! Why are you drinking sake?
What? This is normal.
Here, Kannawa. Your favorite fried tofu!
Ooh! How thoughtful of you!
I feel gross.
See? I warned you!
You okay? Want some water?
No, thanks.
Hey! Why's Kamegawa slumped over?
I bet you forced him to drink that!
No, Senpai.
He did that on his own.
If something happens to Kamegawa,
you're gonna regret it!
Scary!
Overprotective much?
Of course I am.
I told you, he's my precious junior!
What if he wasn't your junior?
Huh?
Are you only being nice to him
because he's your junior?
I don't get what you're saying...
But he's my junior forever!
Got a problem with that?
I don't like that.
I don't want to be your junior forever!
What?
I don't want that, either!
Why would you say that?
I'm also giving it my all,
trying to be the best superior...
So why would you...
Huh?!
Kamegawa, you idiot!
We're so sorry!
Sorry!
Please excuse us!
Have you calmed down a bit?
You two rest here.
I'm going to the baths.
Me, too!
The outdoor baths are amazing.
Really? I'm excited for it.
Let's go together!
Eh? Huh?
WOMEN'S BATH
What?!
That felt great.
Right?
I wanted to find out your true
feelings and took it a bit too far.
Sorry about all the things I said.
Also, I only like Kannawa as a friend.
So don't worry.
Here. Ice cream.
This is yummy.
I like these.
Yeah!
I don't feel as drunk now.
What?!
Kamegawa? Are you okay?!
Kamegawa!
So tired...
I went to a spa, but I'm so tired...
Yu? You're home?
Yeah.
Your face is red.
I had some drinks.
Drinks? With who?
C'mon.
You'll catch a cold, Yu.